<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ramblings on Nailing Jelly</title>
    <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/categories/ramblings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ramblings on Nailing Jelly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 09:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.dotdot.cloud/categories/ramblings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What a long gap...</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2015/05/31/what-a-long-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 09:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2015/05/31/what-a-long-gap/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to write a little more on this blog - admittedly after a 5 year gap its a little difficult to write less!
Anyhow I have a little ranting and a bit of general meandering thought to write down, so here goes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pantomime - This year with comedy stage manager on crutches</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/12/08/pantomime-this-year-with-comedy-stage-manager-on-crutches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/12/08/pantomime-this-year-with-comedy-stage-manager-on-crutches/</guid>
      <description>The start of December for me is Pantomime season - I&amp;rsquo;m the only one of the stage managers at our theatre who is stupid enough or can actually manage to make the time to handle a 2 week run (1 week build/rehearsal, 1 week performance run) - we had previously tried to do this with multiple stage managers each doing a shorter period with less success.
This year things are slightly different - I&amp;rsquo;m not back to full fitness, so am running the show in a slightly more executive mode to normal - ie I tell other people to adjust lights rather than me climbing ladders myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You got what???</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/10/12/you-got-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 15:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/10/12/you-got-what/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve written out variations of this story in various media (try using SMS or twitter) several times over the last 2 weeks, so thought it was worth just putting a batch of stuff down and pointing people here to save my fingers&amp;hellip;. (and memory).
Please be aware that I am being slightly circumspect about some aspects as potentially there is a legal element involved.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also just written this straight out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL::Abstract boolean support</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/09/04/sqlabstract-boolean-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 16:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/09/04/sqlabstract-boolean-support/</guid>
      <description>ribasuschi shipped [SQL::Abstract version 1.58 [earlier today. This version includes the boolean support code I previously [discussed here - with a few additional [bells and whistles merged in more recently.
We&amp;rsquo;ve had a good number of discussions about the best way of doing things, and finally settled on this form of boolean support as a method :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Smokin....?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/24/non-smokin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 11:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/24/non-smokin/</guid>
      <description>Smoke is becoming very much a theme of this week&amp;rsquo;s production.
The strange thing about managing these show runs is the way the work pans out. Typically I am fairly busy during the build period, very very busy during the lighting and technical phases, busy during the rehearsal phase and then relatively lightly loaded during the actual performance run (obviously during the performance itself I have work to do but thats only half the evening, and the time before the performance is quite low impact for most shows).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smokin...</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/18/smokin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 19:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/18/smokin/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m stage managing the musical version of The Railway Children this week. The producing company has seen fit to obtain 4 (really!) smoke machines (and a hazer).
Obviously with all this kit to play with - 2 of the smoke machines were big brutes with DMX interfaces - we needed to test them out. So I rigged one of the DMX controlled ones at the front of stage, set its address, isolated the fire alarm zones covering auditorium, stage, backstage and roof space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So what happened?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/09/so-what-happened/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2009 11:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/09/so-what-happened/</guid>
      <description>Somehow I have been absolutely snowed under for the last 2 months&amp;hellip;
The good bit is that I have the next 10 days on holiday - which means no blogging whatsoever (no change there then).
Hopefully I should be able to actually write something when I get back, although I am starting off with the get in and running of a musical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bletchley Park</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/04/bletchley-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 12:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/04/bletchley-park/</guid>
      <description>There has been a lot of activity on Twitter this morning regarding Bletchley Park - the home of the wartime British decryption effort, and effectively the birthplace of modern computing. Have a look at http://savingbletchleypark.org/ for information.
Bletchley Park is decaying, and in danger of becoming unsustainable - meaning a good chunk of modern computing history will be lost to the world. The normal funding mechanisms (National Lottery etc) have declined to support Bletchley Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favourite stock photo of the year to date</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/02/favourite-stock-photo-of-the-year-to-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 22:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/02/favourite-stock-photo-of-the-year-to-date/</guid>
      <description>So this image is used to illustrate the news story Chaplain to ward off hospital ghost.
I salute the person who decided to go with the bedsheet theme for the illustration.
NB The original image is credited to Getty images - I have just linked to the Guardian copy of the image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relocation....</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/02/relocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 12:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/02/relocation/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m shunting this blog across to wordpress - mainly to be able to use some of the tools available, such as the blogging bundle in TextMate, to handle blog posts.
The main thing is that I have no intention of doing software maintenance on a blogging platform (unless I&amp;rsquo;m being paid for it), so I am sticking with a hosted platform.
You may also find that the theme and layout (assuming you are looking here rather than reading via RSS) may keep changing in the short term until I get to like one look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whats the point of NewsForge</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/08/whats-the-point-of-newsforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2007 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/08/whats-the-point-of-newsforge/</guid>
      <description>I mean, if I want to read linux.com I can go there, so whats the point of having a site that is 95% re-publication of linux.com content - except they only put the first paragraph in, and then link across to linux.com.
Annoyingly NewsForge&amp;rsquo;s RSS feed appears to push stuff out faster than linux.com&amp;rsquo;s so I often see content on there before the same (but in this case complete and original) content appears on the linux.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
