<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nailing Jelly</title>
    <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nailing Jelly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.dotdot.cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Freeserve - How We Built The System</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2021/07/06/freeserve-how-we-built-the-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2021/07/06/freeserve-how-we-built-the-system/</guid>
      <description>“Success has many fathers, but failure is an orphan”
 There have been many people who have claimed to be &amp;ldquo;The Inventor of Freeserve&amp;rdquo;, although in many cases it appears the more fuss they make about this title the less they had to do with it&amp;hellip; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the room when that particular proposal was made (although I have quite strong suspicions on who originally proposed the idea), but I was on the original implementation team within Planet Online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Development Environments</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/10/24/python-development-environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 17:47:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/10/24/python-development-environments/</guid>
      <description>I have spent a substantial number of years mostly programming in Perl, but this year I have been working on a team that has a strong preference for Python and so I have converted across.
Previously I have dabbled in Python - I could read basic python, and had patched various things - mainly Ansible - in the past, but had not done any serious work in the language.
However its not the transfer to the language thats caused most of the headaches, but other things surrounding that - for example:-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Assistant - Bin Collection Display and Notification</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/05/03/home-assistant-bin-collection-display-and-notification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 11:28:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/05/03/home-assistant-bin-collection-display-and-notification/</guid>
      <description>Previously I had built a shim to make it much easier to import data from the York Bin Collections API into Home Assistant
I am making use of this data in two ways:-
 Making a display card in Lovelace to display information about the next bin collection. Making a notification to prod me to put the right bins out.  Lovelace Display This is currently a prototype - and I need to spend more time on working out exactly what I want from the Home Assistant display - I may move to building a substantially minimised display for use with a spare Nook that I have - in a similar way to Turn an old eReader into an Information Screen (Nook STR)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minor Gardening</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/05/02/minor-gardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 19:50:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/05/02/minor-gardening/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve done some tidying of the old posts - mostly this should have zero effect on what you see, but the Markdown has been tidied (line wraps added in to make editing more comfortable), and any internal links should now be internal rather than going back to the previous wordpress site.
Now to actually add some current content&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>York Bins API and Home Assistant</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/04/20/york-bins-api-and-home-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 17:05:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/04/20/york-bins-api-and-home-assistant/</guid>
      <description>I have been using Home Assistant to automate various things at home. One of the things I thought would be useful was the ability for the system to inform me of when the next bin collection is, and what sort of collection this would be.
Thankfully York Council has an API telling you about their bin collections. This is documented at York Waste Collection Lookup
Home Assistant REST Sensors Home Assistant helpfully can use REST sources as a sensor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relocation and Resurrection</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/04/18/relocation-and-resurrection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2020/04/18/relocation-and-resurrection/</guid>
      <description>After a vastly long hiatus (the post 5 years back stating I intended to blog more really doesn&amp;rsquo;t count), I&amp;rsquo;ve finally put something together.
Basically I have a batch of things I am trying out and so want to keep more permanent notes on, hence bringing this back into play.
Hosting Previously I put content onto wordpress.com &amp;ndash; I certainly did not want to get involved in actually managing the blogging platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a long gap...</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2015/05/31/what-a-long-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 09:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2015/05/31/what-a-long-gap/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to write a little more on this blog - admittedly after a 5 year gap its a little difficult to write less!
Anyhow I have a little ranting and a bit of general meandering thought to write down, so here goes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pantomime - This year with comedy stage manager on crutches</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/12/08/pantomime-this-year-with-comedy-stage-manager-on-crutches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/12/08/pantomime-this-year-with-comedy-stage-manager-on-crutches/</guid>
      <description>The start of December for me is Pantomime season - I&amp;rsquo;m the only one of the stage managers at our theatre who is stupid enough or can actually manage to make the time to handle a 2 week run (1 week build/rehearsal, 1 week performance run) - we had previously tried to do this with multiple stage managers each doing a shorter period with less success.
This year things are slightly different - I&amp;rsquo;m not back to full fitness, so am running the show in a slightly more executive mode to normal - ie I tell other people to adjust lights rather than me climbing ladders myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You got what???</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/10/12/you-got-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 15:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/10/12/you-got-what/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve written out variations of this story in various media (try using SMS or twitter) several times over the last 2 weeks, so thought it was worth just putting a batch of stuff down and pointing people here to save my fingers&amp;hellip;. (and memory).
Please be aware that I am being slightly circumspect about some aspects as potentially there is a legal element involved.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also just written this straight out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics - Just the same old same old</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/10/07/politics-just-the-same-old-same-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 13:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/10/07/politics-just-the-same-old-same-old/</guid>
      <description>In the UK we are getting to the end of the political conference season, with lots of people earnestly telling us their ideas for government which will be tossed aside as soon as the inconvenience of a poll can disposed of.
For me the problem is that I don&amp;rsquo;t want solutions as much as I want revenge.
Seriously, the people responsible for all bad decisions made, basically take no rap for the problems they cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL::Abstract boolean support</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/09/04/sqlabstract-boolean-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 16:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/09/04/sqlabstract-boolean-support/</guid>
      <description>ribasuschi shipped [SQL::Abstract version 1.58 [earlier today. This version includes the boolean support code I previously [discussed here - with a few additional [bells and whistles merged in more recently.
We&amp;rsquo;ve had a good number of discussions about the best way of doing things, and finally settled on this form of boolean support as a method :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPAN RPM  Packaging</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/06/03/cpan-rpm-packaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 19:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/06/03/cpan-rpm-packaging/</guid>
      <description>Seeing as I have been asked about building RPM packages of CPAN modules today I thought it was worth putting some information down in a blog post - I would love comments on this, so that I can improve the information and hopefully make my processes better.
Firstly, I target Centos 4 and 5 i386 only, although I am going to have to start building for x86_64 too) and build stuff for our own internal requirements, the latter meaning that the stuff I package depends very much one what I need for work at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XML Processing</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/06/01/xml-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 20:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/06/01/xml-processing/</guid>
      <description>Recently I have had to revisit one of our systems that deal with XML call records (from a VOIP switch).
This system splits out Call Detail Records (CDRs) by customer. The version of this that was running was based on XML::Twig which used to run acceptably fast (this code was written a number of years ago), and has the advantage of being relatively light on memory as the document was processed a chunk at a time rather than being completely read into memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extending SQL::Abstract</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/05/11/extending-sqlabstract/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 19:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/05/11/extending-sqlabstract/</guid>
      <description>Most of the perl I write currently has ties into DBIx::Class and hence uses SQL::Abstract.
I also have far too much of a preference for boolean items, which I normally encode in the database as a column of type boolean (or the SQLite vague equivalent).
Its been fairly easy to encode a test for boolean value being true with SQL::Abstract - although the syntax
column =&amp;gt; \&#39;&#39;  which maps to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theatre Management with Perl - 1</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/05/03/theatre-management-with-perl-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 21:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/05/03/theatre-management-with-perl-1/</guid>
      <description>First some history - in fact this post is almost all history and setting the scene for what we did later.
When I joined the theatre there was a website - however it had been done by someone&amp;rsquo;s friend, and was a flash only movie containing information on the shows that were coming in the near future. This suffered massively from being done in spare time and could take months to get updated, so something had to be done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gadget Drooling</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/29/gadget-drooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 20:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/29/gadget-drooling/</guid>
      <description>Spent yesterday at PLASA Focus at Leeds Royal Armouries.
We went with a fair shopping list - both Lighting Desk and Sound Desk as well as considering what to do about Radio Microphones (the Government playing silly buggers with frequency allocations makes this one a tricky prospect).
We also ended up considering smoke and haze machines - our own is somewhat long in the tooth, and we are considering keeping this sort of equipment in house but charging hirers a fee for use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enlightened Ironman?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/27/enlightened-ironman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 12:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/27/enlightened-ironman/</guid>
      <description>Following the blog post and proposal from Matt Trout, I&amp;rsquo;m going to aim to push out some posts on my uses and experiences of perl. I&amp;rsquo;m extraordinarily unlikely to hit the Ironman rating since a look back at my history shows the occaisional year between posts :-)
Anyhow, as an ancient perl user (I pulled a perl release from usenet back sometime around 1988/89), I have quite a lot of odds of perl around, although mostly I have been pretty good at retiring the stuff that has outstayed its useful life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Smokin....?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/24/non-smokin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 11:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/24/non-smokin/</guid>
      <description>Smoke is becoming very much a theme of this week&amp;rsquo;s production.
The strange thing about managing these show runs is the way the work pans out. Typically I am fairly busy during the build period, very very busy during the lighting and technical phases, busy during the rehearsal phase and then relatively lightly loaded during the actual performance run (obviously during the performance itself I have work to do but thats only half the evening, and the time before the performance is quite low impact for most shows).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smokin...</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/18/smokin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 19:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/18/smokin/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m stage managing the musical version of The Railway Children this week. The producing company has seen fit to obtain 4 (really!) smoke machines (and a hazer).
Obviously with all this kit to play with - 2 of the smoke machines were big brutes with DMX interfaces - we needed to test them out. So I rigged one of the DMX controlled ones at the front of stage, set its address, isolated the fire alarm zones covering auditorium, stage, backstage and roof space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So what happened?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/09/so-what-happened/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2009 11:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/09/so-what-happened/</guid>
      <description>Somehow I have been absolutely snowed under for the last 2 months&amp;hellip;
The good bit is that I have the next 10 days on holiday - which means no blogging whatsoever (no change there then).
Hopefully I should be able to actually write something when I get back, although I am starting off with the get in and running of a musical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bletchley Park</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/04/bletchley-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 12:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/04/bletchley-park/</guid>
      <description>There has been a lot of activity on Twitter this morning regarding Bletchley Park - the home of the wartime British decryption effort, and effectively the birthplace of modern computing. Have a look at http://savingbletchleypark.org/ for information.
Bletchley Park is decaying, and in danger of becoming unsustainable - meaning a good chunk of modern computing history will be lost to the world. The normal funding mechanisms (National Lottery etc) have declined to support Bletchley Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favourite stock photo of the year to date</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/02/favourite-stock-photo-of-the-year-to-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 22:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/02/favourite-stock-photo-of-the-year-to-date/</guid>
      <description>So this image is used to illustrate the news story Chaplain to ward off hospital ghost.
I salute the person who decided to go with the bedsheet theme for the illustration.
NB The original image is credited to Getty images - I have just linked to the Guardian copy of the image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relocation....</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/02/relocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 12:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/02/02/relocation/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m shunting this blog across to wordpress - mainly to be able to use some of the tools available, such as the blogging bundle in TextMate, to handle blog posts.
The main thing is that I have no intention of doing software maintenance on a blogging platform (unless I&amp;rsquo;m being paid for it), so I am sticking with a hosted platform.
You may also find that the theme and layout (assuming you are looking here rather than reading via RSS) may keep changing in the short term until I get to like one look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 12:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a sysadmin-come-software-engineer who escaped from the world of pseudo-hardware many years back (used to do VLSI design).
I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved with free software for many years, with linux for more than 25, and mail systems for a similar length of time&amp;hellip;. and I also stage manage for a local theatre, which can give an odd mix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theatrical Going Ons</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/01/31/theatrical-going-ons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/01/31/theatrical-going-ons/</guid>
      <description>Currently the theatre is dark - there is 4 weeks of work being done on the heating system (conveniently in one of the colder periods).
A week back I did my first show of the year - a dance show with a company that I haven&amp;rsquo;t worked with before, although thats not too suprising since they only put a show on in alternate years. This dance school was fun to work with - well behaved, hard working and technically very good, however it was hard work because the staging aspects - lighting and set requirements - were being revealed to us as we went along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Return</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/01/30/the-return/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2009 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/01/30/the-return/</guid>
      <description>Hmm.. it&amp;rsquo;s been a while. A very long while in fact.
However I think I will resurrect this blog - I did wonder about quietly killing it and starting another rather than have the embarassment of an 18 month gap in posting, but I&amp;rsquo;ll live with that for now. We can at least see where it goes from here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still tired...</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/06/10/still-tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/06/10/still-tired/</guid>
      <description>So we finished the run of How To Succeed In Business&amp;hellip; last night with a pretty good performance, followed by one of the best aided get-outs I have ever seen - we had a good sized bunch of people helping, cheerfully, get the set out, everything cleaned up, and finally repainting the stage floor - the stage surface is hardboard with normally a coat of graphite grey paint on it, if someone wishes it a different colour for a show we have to return it to normal afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Bees</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/06/02/more-bees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2007 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/06/02/more-bees/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back in theatre again - this time to stage manage a production of How To Succeed in Business Without Really Trying.
The bees are also back. There were many wandering around and dying on stage in the morning - then I found one on a cloth I was tying up to a flying bar (it didn&amp;rsquo;t like being found and stung me).
Setting lights was a problem because the things are attracted to them when on</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Happy Mac</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/09/not-happy-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2007 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/09/not-happy-mac/</guid>
      <description>My MacBook has managed to trash my preferences again - not too drastic maybe, except that also means its lost all my Mail settings (glad the mail itself is on imap) and all the calendar settings including the actual entries&amp;hellip;.
It looks like changing the video setup whilst it is suspended is a good way to break things - suspend then unplug the external video and open it up again without the external video, and it can hang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whats the point of NewsForge</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/08/whats-the-point-of-newsforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2007 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/08/whats-the-point-of-newsforge/</guid>
      <description>I mean, if I want to read linux.com I can go there, so whats the point of having a site that is 95% re-publication of linux.com content - except they only put the first paragraph in, and then link across to linux.com.
Annoyingly NewsForge&amp;rsquo;s RSS feed appears to push stuff out faster than linux.com&amp;rsquo;s so I often see content on there before the same (but in this case complete and original) content appears on the linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good news...</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/06/good-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/06/good-news/</guid>
      <description>[Reid to resign with Blair - if [only a few of the other [utterly incompetent idiots would go to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Bands and Bums</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/06/of-bands-and-bums/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/06/of-bands-and-bums/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was spent in the theatre dealing with a wind band concert.
At one level this is a lot of fun - this band are a good bunch who are enthusiastic, have a lot of ideas although they vary between good organisation and a level of anarchy.
On another level its a real slog - in the first hour we got out and placed just about all our staging blocks (close on 40, roughly 1 meter square blocks which are stored in a 3 or 4 high stack on their sides behind the stage backwall (cyclorama) - extracting them is seriously hard work because the bracing behind the cyclorama means that you have to manoever the blocks over the bracing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of browsers and software</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/23/of-browsers-and-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/23/of-browsers-and-software/</guid>
      <description>Firefox has been crawling for [me recently. I mostly fixed this today by uninstalling [Google Desktop from my [MacBook.
However I also fired up Opera - boy did it feel fast next to Firefox. I really do like the cross browser sync features of Google Browser Sync which allows me to keep home and office in sync, and things like Web Developer (which is only an occasional use, but invaluable), however Opera is a very nice browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theatrical matters</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/23/theatrical-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/23/theatrical-matters/</guid>
      <description>A gap in blogging - I have been running a show in theatre for the last week, which leaves little time for anything else (sleep is short too).
The main things learned, are never expect a stage gun to work - in fact expect anything technical to play games given the chance&amp;hellip;
The abiding sound of the week was the click click click click bang of one of the stagehands attempting to get a working gunshot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini summit?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/13/mini-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/13/mini-summit/</guid>
      <description>.. and don&amp;rsquo;t get me started on the absurdity of &amp;lsquo;mini-summit&amp;rsquo;.
I think you will find thats a Hump</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtualisation</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/03/31/virtualisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2007 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/03/31/virtualisation/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking at virtualisation recently - both for use within my group and for wider use with the company.
We need to be able to handle Windows VMs as well as proper operating systems, so unfortunately things like Open VZ or its commercial cousin Virtuozzo are not an option, which pretty much leaves Xen (both the Linux distribution hosted version and the Xensource packaged version) and VMWare. Live migration of VMs would be useful, although for its overkill for our group requirements (but having it means we can test how things work in a clustered environment with migration, so its down as a really want if not a must have).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handling Mail</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/03/27/handling-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2007 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/03/27/handling-mail/</guid>
      <description>I pretty much live by email. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it for around 25 years now, and have had good access to internet email for close on 20 years. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on open development mailing lists for all of that time, and have at times been receiving many hundreds (if not thousands) of messages a day.
I obviously don&amp;rsquo;t read all those messages - not in detail - and since I maintain a bunch of machines that send all sorts of general notification mail, much of it is glanced at (ie just look at sender and subject) and either ignored or deleted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
