<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mac on Nailing Jelly</title>
    <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/categories/mac/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mac on Nailing Jelly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2007 21:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.dotdot.cloud/categories/mac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Not Happy Mac</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/09/not-happy-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2007 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/09/not-happy-mac/</guid>
      <description>My MacBook has managed to trash my preferences again - not too drastic maybe, except that also means its lost all my Mail settings (glad the mail itself is on imap) and all the calendar settings including the actual entries&amp;hellip;.
It looks like changing the video setup whilst it is suspended is a good way to break things - suspend then unplug the external video and open it up again without the external video, and it can hang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of browsers and software</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/23/of-browsers-and-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/23/of-browsers-and-software/</guid>
      <description>Firefox has been crawling for [me recently. I mostly fixed this today by uninstalling [Google Desktop from my [MacBook.
However I also fired up Opera - boy did it feel fast next to Firefox. I really do like the cross browser sync features of Google Browser Sync which allows me to keep home and office in sync, and things like Web Developer (which is only an occasional use, but invaluable), however Opera is a very nice browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handling Mail</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/03/27/handling-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2007 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/03/27/handling-mail/</guid>
      <description>I pretty much live by email. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it for around 25 years now, and have had good access to internet email for close on 20 years. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on open development mailing lists for all of that time, and have at times been receiving many hundreds (if not thousands) of messages a day.
I obviously don&amp;rsquo;t read all those messages - not in detail - and since I maintain a bunch of machines that send all sorts of general notification mail, much of it is glanced at (ie just look at sender and subject) and either ignored or deleted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
