<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>theatre on Nailing Jelly</title>
    <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/categories/theatre/</link>
    <description>Recent content in theatre on Nailing Jelly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 12:39:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.dotdot.cloud/categories/theatre/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pantomime - This year with comedy stage manager on crutches</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/12/08/pantomime-this-year-with-comedy-stage-manager-on-crutches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/12/08/pantomime-this-year-with-comedy-stage-manager-on-crutches/</guid>
      <description>The start of December for me is Pantomime season - I&amp;rsquo;m the only one of the stage managers at our theatre who is stupid enough or can actually manage to make the time to handle a 2 week run (1 week build/rehearsal, 1 week performance run) - we had previously tried to do this with multiple stage managers each doing a shorter period with less success.
This year things are slightly different - I&amp;rsquo;m not back to full fitness, so am running the show in a slightly more executive mode to normal - ie I tell other people to adjust lights rather than me climbing ladders myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theatre Management with Perl - 1</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/05/03/theatre-management-with-perl-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 21:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/05/03/theatre-management-with-perl-1/</guid>
      <description>First some history - in fact this post is almost all history and setting the scene for what we did later.
When I joined the theatre there was a website - however it had been done by someone&amp;rsquo;s friend, and was a flash only movie containing information on the shows that were coming in the near future. This suffered massively from being done in spare time and could take months to get updated, so something had to be done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gadget Drooling</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/29/gadget-drooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 20:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/29/gadget-drooling/</guid>
      <description>Spent yesterday at PLASA Focus at Leeds Royal Armouries.
We went with a fair shopping list - both Lighting Desk and Sound Desk as well as considering what to do about Radio Microphones (the Government playing silly buggers with frequency allocations makes this one a tricky prospect).
We also ended up considering smoke and haze machines - our own is somewhat long in the tooth, and we are considering keeping this sort of equipment in house but charging hirers a fee for use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enlightened Ironman?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/27/enlightened-ironman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 12:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/27/enlightened-ironman/</guid>
      <description>Following the blog post and proposal from Matt Trout, I&amp;rsquo;m going to aim to push out some posts on my uses and experiences of perl. I&amp;rsquo;m extraordinarily unlikely to hit the Ironman rating since a look back at my history shows the occaisional year between posts :-)
Anyhow, as an ancient perl user (I pulled a perl release from usenet back sometime around 1988/89), I have quite a lot of odds of perl around, although mostly I have been pretty good at retiring the stuff that has outstayed its useful life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Smokin....?</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/24/non-smokin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 11:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/24/non-smokin/</guid>
      <description>Smoke is becoming very much a theme of this week&amp;rsquo;s production.
The strange thing about managing these show runs is the way the work pans out. Typically I am fairly busy during the build period, very very busy during the lighting and technical phases, busy during the rehearsal phase and then relatively lightly loaded during the actual performance run (obviously during the performance itself I have work to do but thats only half the evening, and the time before the performance is quite low impact for most shows).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smokin...</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/18/smokin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 19:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/04/18/smokin/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m stage managing the musical version of The Railway Children this week. The producing company has seen fit to obtain 4 (really!) smoke machines (and a hazer).
Obviously with all this kit to play with - 2 of the smoke machines were big brutes with DMX interfaces - we needed to test them out. So I rigged one of the DMX controlled ones at the front of stage, set its address, isolated the fire alarm zones covering auditorium, stage, backstage and roof space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theatrical Going Ons</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/01/31/theatrical-going-ons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2009 22:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2009/01/31/theatrical-going-ons/</guid>
      <description>Currently the theatre is dark - there is 4 weeks of work being done on the heating system (conveniently in one of the colder periods).
A week back I did my first show of the year - a dance show with a company that I haven&amp;rsquo;t worked with before, although thats not too suprising since they only put a show on in alternate years. This dance school was fun to work with - well behaved, hard working and technically very good, however it was hard work because the staging aspects - lighting and set requirements - were being revealed to us as we went along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still tired...</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/06/10/still-tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2007 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/06/10/still-tired/</guid>
      <description>So we finished the run of How To Succeed In Business&amp;hellip; last night with a pretty good performance, followed by one of the best aided get-outs I have ever seen - we had a good sized bunch of people helping, cheerfully, get the set out, everything cleaned up, and finally repainting the stage floor - the stage surface is hardboard with normally a coat of graphite grey paint on it, if someone wishes it a different colour for a show we have to return it to normal afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Bees</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/06/02/more-bees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2007 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/06/02/more-bees/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back in theatre again - this time to stage manage a production of How To Succeed in Business Without Really Trying.
The bees are also back. There were many wandering around and dying on stage in the morning - then I found one on a cloth I was tying up to a flying bar (it didn&amp;rsquo;t like being found and stung me).
Setting lights was a problem because the things are attracted to them when on</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Bands and Bums</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/06/of-bands-and-bums/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2007 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/05/06/of-bands-and-bums/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was spent in the theatre dealing with a wind band concert.
At one level this is a lot of fun - this band are a good bunch who are enthusiastic, have a lot of ideas although they vary between good organisation and a level of anarchy.
On another level its a real slog - in the first hour we got out and placed just about all our staging blocks (close on 40, roughly 1 meter square blocks which are stored in a 3 or 4 high stack on their sides behind the stage backwall (cyclorama) - extracting them is seriously hard work because the bracing behind the cyclorama means that you have to manoever the blocks over the bracing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theatrical matters</title>
      <link>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/23/theatrical-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2007 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dotdot.cloud/2007/04/23/theatrical-matters/</guid>
      <description>A gap in blogging - I have been running a show in theatre for the last week, which leaves little time for anything else (sleep is short too).
The main things learned, are never expect a stage gun to work - in fact expect anything technical to play games given the chance&amp;hellip;
The abiding sound of the week was the click click click click bang of one of the stagehands attempting to get a working gunshot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
